common for you to have storms and heavy rains during the monsoon season, but along with this,
we must have seen that
many trees on the road are also found
surrounded by storms. Many times it happens
that they fall on cars or bikes, causing a
lot of damage. These are the
reports. Now, in the monsoon season,
if your vehicle or a tree gets
surrounded by rain due to storm or hurricane, then
what kind of insurance should you have for that
and how can you get it?
[Music]
If you too have taken action due to natural calamities like storm and a
tree falls, causing
damage, then let me tell you
that it is mandatory for you to have comprehensive motor
insurance because
insurance is mandatory in case of any natural calamity
like earthquake, rain or landslide, etc.
Due to this, you can
easily compensate for your loss. Not only this,
if your bike gets stolen, then there is
such motor insurance
which is useful here only. Now we
will tell you that if you have comprehensive motor
insurance, then you can get it.  How
can you clean it? Let us see the step
by step process. First of all,
register clearly on the toll free number of your insurance company
and keep this number with you so that it is
easy to tell the telemarketer.
After this, you can register your vehicle with a nearby
mechanic shop.
You can get the details about this from your company's customer care.
Fill a work form along with all the documents.
Submit it and submit the claim form.
You will
easily get this information on the insurance company's website. So,
after applying here, the insurance
company has sent a survey.
After the combination, some companies
also provide the facility of video survey. So,
you
can also ask for a copy of all these documents. So, when all these things are
ready and the work is completed, then the
insurance claim is made
and after this, finally you will have to do
it continuously
and you cannot get information about this.
To see this information and videos, you can visit
our website here.com  You can log in
and don't forget to subscribe to our YouTube channel.
Thank you
[Music]